[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[The content, events, techniques, and outcomes of massage depicted in this series]
[are entirely fictional and intended for entertainment purposes only.]
[They should not be used as medical advice or as a reference for traditional Thai massage.]
[Viewer discretion is advised. Do not attempt to imitate any of the techniques shown,]
[as doing so may result in injury.]
[Massage services should only be provided by practitioners]
[who are legally licensed and registered.]
Not one of them is any good.
Bring me someone else.
I know a younger therapist at the massage shop where I used to work.
She’s an excellent masseuse.
- I don't think so. - Call her in.
You mean Dongyang?
Yes. He asked me to give him a Kasai massage. His little bird wouldn’t sing.
Areeya recommended this therapist.
The one you once lectured.
She has great hands
even better than yours.
You remind me of another therapist.
- Who was it? - That therapist is fucking dead.
Ittha, Pingkhala,
Sumana, Kalathari,
Sahatsarangsi,
Thawari, Chanthaphusang.
Hey!
Are you one of them?
How did you know that someone was trying to kill me?
I didn't know.
How the hell do you not know? Where is your brain?
Didn't you even ask when they sent you here?
I'm just glad you're safe.
You're Phat, right?
Yes, sir.
Thanks for getting here just in time.
They'd better hope I don't find out who they're working for.
Who sent you? Tell me right now.
Or I'll shoot you right here.
Easy, Dongyang.
No assassin would go through massage training just to kill someone.
And she's damn good at it, too.
Who sent you to kill me?
Who sent you?
She just... she was only contacted to give you a massage for your condition.
Phat.
Take her to the hospital.
Then take her home.
Yes, sir.
Ms. Hattha, your prescription is ready.
Ms. Hattha, what's your last name?
Niphakornkul.
- Are you allergic to any medications? - Nope.
This is an antibiotic.
Take one tablet after each meal until it's finished.
And this is a painkiller.
If you're in pain, you can take it after meals as well.
But if you have an allergic reaction to either medication
or your condition doesn't improve,
please come back and see the doctor right away.
That's everything.
Where do you live?
I can get home by myself.
I was told to take you home.
He can order you around, but he can't order me around.
Ow! It hurts!
Hey!
Stay still.
Hey! Hey!
Where do you live?
So where do you live?
Then stay at my place tonight.
Talat Phlu.
Hey! What happened?
You...
Come on. Get inside. Go.
[Hattha's House]
What the fuck?
Did everything go smoothly today?
Yes. Mr. Dongyang is safe.
Get ready to become Dongyang's bodyguard.
Keep an eye on him.
Yes, Dad.
Don't let anyone find out who you are.
Phat!
Get to the hospital and check on your mom right now!
Hurry up!
Phat, come here.
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
I'm so sorry. Don't leave me.
- Mom! - My son, Patrick.
Stay with Dad.
Listen to him, please.
I love you.
I love you too, Mom.
I'm so sorry.
Love you, Mom.
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
No.
What about Dad?
Just come upstairs. Don't be stubborn.
Stay here with us.
Be good, so Dad will love you.
Wan.
I'm sorry. I'll be more careful next time.
I'll take better care of myself.
But the doctor said it's not that serious.
The wound isn't that deep. I'm tough, you know.
Isn't there any other way?
This is the only way.
Get close, then disappear without a trace.
I'm gonna get him back.
You give him a relaxing massage while you're the one getting hurt.
These things take time.
Damn, I can pee so easily now.
Damn, she's really good at massages.
I've already treated some of his symptoms with massage.
And I drugged him, too.
He'll probably call me back for another massage soon.
Drugged him?
You bastard!
Give me a hand.
Did you hit a nerve again?
I'll kill him before he even realizes what's happening.
- She uses the Kamdon pressure point. - [The Kamdon point is used in massage to relieve neck pain and headaches.]
- [It's located in the hollow beneath the base of the skull.] - It's a key pressure point
that can affect the blood vessels in the neck.
That's a dangerous pressure point, isn't it?
What does that have to do with the Kasai massage, Master?
Come here.
Master.
[WARNING: The massage techniques depicted in this series are entirely fictional.]
- [Do not attempt to imitate them.] - Master?
I'm sorry.
I barely pressed it and you couldn't even take the pain.
So why would that girl press that point on Dongyang?
Why would she do it?
Why?
What?
Work on the piriformis muscle, too.
I fell down the stairs, so my legs've been acting up.
Your legs acted up first.
That's what made you fall down the stairs.
That masseur drugged you.
Try moving it.
Damn, that's good.
That bitch!
I should've killed her.
She wasn't trying to seriously hurt you.
She's just keeping you from fully recovering
so you'll call her back for another massage.
What kind of fucking therapist keeps her customers sick?
Muk, tell that fucking therapist
to come massage me again in three days.
Dad.
What are we doing?
I fought them before,
and it cost us your mother and your brother.
How can people like us fight them?
Exactly.
What can we possibly do with just our bare hands?
Uncle.
Where's Dad, Wan?
Dad.
Minkheng and Wan.
- Yes? - Search everywhere.
What are you looking for?
Excuse me.
Dad, what are you looking for?
- Find anything, Minkheng? - Not yet.
I'm asking what you're looking for.
Dad, what are you looking for?
Push the cabinet.
They think our whole family is dead.
That the only one left is a harmless little girl.
If they find out you're planning to take revenge,
they'll never let us live.
We can't fight them.
Can't we fight them, or are we just refusing to fight?
I'm not refusing to fight because I'm scared.
And I didn't run away
because I'm a coward.
I just can't lose another child.
Dad, don't ever forget that they killed Mom and Phak
and left you like this.
And it's because I am still like that.
And you're just a woman.
What can we possibly do against them?
Hattha.
He's dead.
- Korn, you lied to me. - Hey! What are you doing?
- Tim, let him go. - You know how to kill someone with massage, right?
- Right? Korn? - Let go!
- Tim, calm down. - I told you I just got here.
I don't know what to do so you'd believe me.
[WARNING: The massage techniques depicted in this series are entirely fictional.]
[Do not attempt to imitate them.]
We should hide here.
Korn!
Korn! Inn!
About that killer massage manual...
I believe you now. It doesn't exist.
I'm serious.
You two are my family.
Of course you're more important to me than some stupid manual.
You two are running away from me, aren't you?
Fine. Then keep running forever.
You'd better hope I never find you.
Uncle! Uncle!
Uncle!
Why?
Why did this happen?
Why did you let that girl massage him again, Master?
You saw that he hurt Mr. Dongyang.
Do you know why Dongyang fell down the stairs?
You think that girl did it on purpose, Master?
[WARNING: The massage techniques depicted in this series are entirely fictional.]
[Do not attempt to imitate them.]
The same pressure point
can be used for healing or can be dangerous.
It all depends on whether the masseur is skilled enough.
And you definitely aren't.
Go to the room.
I'm on my period today.
I need you to help me with something.
[Wan]
A cramp?
I'm fine now.
But your head still feels heavy, right?
When you get a cramp, your whole body tenses up.
The pressure rises to your head.
I'll release it for you.
What else do you want from me?
Stay.
Just sit still.
Feel better?
How well do you know Dongyang?
I don't know him.
I was just following orders.
Whose orders?
What are you planning to do now?
I was just asking.
Fine, I won't ask.
But keep massaging me.
I'll pay you.
I'm expensive.
And I don't take money.
Anything. If it's something I can give you.
Mm.
You're stressed, aren't you?
Sometimes you need to let things go.
It'll help loosen up these tight muscles a little.
Sometimes you have to let yourself make mistakes.
It's exhausting trying to be good all the time.
Where are you headed?
Oh, we're going to the orchard in Rayong, sir.
Here you go.
- Go ahead. - Yes, sir.
- Go. - Wait.
Wait, Sergeant.
Captain, there's a sticker.
We'll need to search the vehicle.
Step out of the truck.
Get out.
Open it. Hurry.
Hey, what's that sound?
- What's the sound? - Hey! Run!
Hey! Follow them!
Search the truck, now.
What?
Sir? There are people.
- Help them! - Okay.
Calm down, just calm down.
I told you, it's your job to take care of this for me.
I've already paid you a fortune.
Yeah, I'm holding it over you.
Everyone in this damn country can be bought.
You're not the only one.
We believe that high-ranking government officials
are working with this foreign criminal syndicate.
No matter who's involved,
I'll make sure they're all brought to justice.
I'll root out this entire illicit operation
to restore the honor of Thai civil servants.
Root out my ass.
What fucking honor? What a load of bullshit.
Set up a meeting with Desmond and Xing out at sea this Friday.
I'll settle everything with both of them at once and get this shit over with.
Sure, Boss.
Fuck!
I'm leaving.
You're just getting better.
I think you should skip it this month.
I can call Luang Por and let him know.
People are waiting for you to treat them. You can't just leave them waiting.
Where are you going, Dad?
Aren't you going to give massages to the elderly at the temple?
I'm coming with you.
Come on. Let's go.
Go.
Ya, you don't have to go to the temple today. I'll go instead.
What? Don't you have somewhere else to be?
Not anymore.
[Free Thai Massage for Health by Volunteer Massage Therapists]
That's Hattha.
She comes to treat the elderly here every month.
She's been doing it for years, since before she even graduated.
Her father's here to help so it's even better.
Otherwise, she'd be here until evening.
Sometimes it gets dark before she's done.
The man in the wheelchair?
Don't let that fool you. He's a great masseur.
He used to run a massage shop in Phuket years ago.
Does her father live in Phuket?
Not anymore.
But he comes by every once in a while.
This is my dad's shop. You can go there.
[Phuket Massage Shop Fire in 2011]
[Deadly Phuket Fire Guts Famous 'Our Home' Massage Shop]
[Tragedy: One Dead, One Missing, One Miraculous Survivor]
[Master Tim: How's it going?]
Nothing suspicious, sir.
Hey.
It's your first day, too?
I'm Boat.
Phat.
Let's go.
This bitch tried to run, Boss.
I'm scared. I won't run again.
You don't die just from losing an arm.
Trust me, I know this stuff.
You gotta keep hacking at her until she dies.
Boss! Boss, she's dead.
Good.
The last guard couldn't stomach it.
He killed the woman before I was done.
So I shot the bastard.
Fucking idiot, trying to play hero.
Did you find it, Inn?
It's okay. Thanks a lot.
Let's go, Uncle. It's late.
Minkheng.
Has Hattha ever gone through any of my storage boxes?
No, I don't think so.
Oh, actually, there was one time.
It was not long after you moved to Photharam.
She asked me for the key so she could look for a herbal compress recipe.
Please don't let it be what I think it is.
[Massage Dongyang – 9:00 AM]
[Saturday, August 29, 2026, 9:00–10:00 AM]
[DO NOT READ]
You're going to die by my hand, Dongyang.
Wan, she's left.
Yes, Uncle.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Where's Mr. Dongyang?
He wanted you to wait here.
Wait, wait.
Hey—oh.
What the hell?
[Wan]
She's not answering, Uncle.
But the GPS says she's in this building.
Uncle, I'll go down and check.
Wait here, okay?
Minkheng, keep an eye on him. Call me if anything happens.
May I see your VIP membership card, please?
He's a regular of mine.
Muk.
What are you doing here?
I'm lost.
You think I'm lying.
I can smell it.
The smell again?
Hey, wait. Hold on.
And you're afraid of something, too.
My senses are more acute than most people's.
My sense of smell, I mean.
You're stressed.
And you probably don't believe what I'm telling you.
What exactly do you want here?
You smell nice.
That means deep down, you're a good person.
I want you to believe that I have no intention of hurting anyone.
Especially a good person like you.
After you.
Hurry.
- What? - Come on.
Where are we going?
Oh, aren't I massaging Mr. Dongyang here?
Good luck, okay?
I'll handle it.
Uncle, that's her.
Call Wan. Quick.
Okay.
This is your father's massage shop, isn't it?
Don't worry. Dongyang doesn't know.
Is it or isn't it?
This place is more dangerous than you think.
Has he picked up yet?
No.
Get in the van. Mr. Dongyang is waiting.
- Come on, just get in. - Go.
- You need to sit in the front. - Okay.
Uncle?
- Wan, they grabbed her and took her away in a van. - Got it.
Hurry up and follow them.
Do you usually offer special sessions?
The motorway?
Where are they taking her?
Get out.
Hurry.
Go.
Let's go around the back, Uncle.
Mr. Dongyang told you to wait here.
Then where is Mr. Dongyang?
He has some business to take care of.
When he's ready, he'll send someone to pick you up.
Hey, go wait at the boat.
Minkheng.
Wait here. Call me if anything happens.
I'll be right back.
- Be careful. - Okay.
Uncle?
I think I forgot my phone in the car.
Go get it and hurry back.
Okay.
That asshole causing trouble again?
Yeah. I'm on my way to see him.
- Dongyang? - If he can't do anything about it,
I will ask someone else.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
Yeah, don't worry.
I've called everyone in this time.
Desmond and Xing will both be there.
Huh?
Hey!
You! Stop!
You bastard.
Yeah, I'm here.
I'm on my way. Yeah.
[Mr. Dongyang]
Yes, Mr. Dongyang?
Only the hostesses are going on the boat?
Yes, sir. Got it.
Can I go massage Mr. Dongyang now?
He only asked for the hostesses, not you.
Mr. Dongyang's in a really bad mood.
I don't think you'll be giving him a massage today.
Looks like you came all this way for nothing.
Hey, tell the girls to get dressed and take them to the boat.
Mr. Dongyang's really pissed off.
Hurry up.
Yeah.
Hey!
Where are you going?
The bathroom.
You're following me this closely. Wanna come into the bathroom with me too?
Mr. Krit?
Hello, Mr. Krit.
I'm Hattha. Do you remember me?
Hattha?
My parents owned a massage shop called Our Home Thai Massage.
Ah, the one in Phuket, right?
Yes.
I've seen you in the news.
How have you been?
I've been well.
What brings you here? Are you here for fun?
Oh, I'm a massage therapist. I'm waiting for a client.
What brings you here, sir?
I'm here to meet some important people.
Politics. It's boring.
What about you? Who are you living with these days?
I'm staying with Wan, Dr. Inn's son.
Ah. Give them my regards.
It's good that you became a massage therapist like your father.
If your father were still here, he'd be proud of you.
I should get going now.
Of course. Goodbye.
- Hello? - How was it?
I just walked her to the bathroom.
How are things over there?
Everyone's here.
Once Mr. Dongyang gets here, we can set sail.
- Send me updates. - Sure.
Yeah, I'm at the bathroom. Let me check.
Shit.
I really got my period. I'm screwed.
What if I get on the boat and he wants me? What am I gonna do?
Dongyang's fucking crazy. I'm not risking it.
What if he throws me overboard like Ning?
Li, are you in Pattaya?
There's seriously no one available?
Yeah. If I can't find a replacement for tonight,
we're all totally screwed.
Can you find someone for me?
I need her here right now. I'll pay extra.
Are you looking for someone to take your place on the boat?
I can take your place. I won't even charge you.
But you have to do something for me.
What are you waiting for?
I thought you were fucking dead.
I massaged you so you could walk again.